Finding Aid for Eclipse Jazz (University of Michigan) records, 1975-1987
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Eclipse Jazz (University of Michigan) records 1975-1987
Eclipse Jazz (University of Michigan).
2.5 linear feet
87334 Bimu F71 2
University of Michigan student organization founded to promote interest in jazz through concert and lecture series. Audio-tapes of lectures, photographs, posters, announcements of concerts, newsletters, grant files, and scattered correspondence.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The record group was received from the organization (donor no. 7444 )
No further additions to the records are expected.
The collection is open to research.
Eclipse Jazz was a University of Michigan student organization founded to promote interest in jazz through a series of concerts and lectures.
The Eclipse Jazz records include photographs, sound records of the various lectures and concerts, posters and flyer notices of concerts, and miscellaneous administrative materials, such as grant applications, correspondence, and newsletters of their activities.
Subjects:
Eclipse Jazz (University of Michigan); Jazz--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Music--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Musicians--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; University of Michigan--Students--Societies, etc.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Eclipse Jazz (University of Michigan); Jazz music.; Ann Arbor Art Fairs (Ann Arbor, Mich.); Michigan Union.; Musicians.; University of Michigan--Students--Societies, etc.
Subjects - Sound Recordings:
Eclipse Jazz (University of Michigan); Jazz--Michigan.
Genre Terms:
Photographs.; Posters.; Sound recordings.
- Photographs
  - Performers, A-W, 4 folders (Box 1)
  - Performers, unidentified (Box 1)
  - Eclipse staff and office (Box 1)
  - Summer concerts (Box 1)
  - Art Fair (Box 1)
- Sound recordings of lecture series, 10 in. reel-to-reel; 7 1/2 ips
  - James Dapogny, October 11, 1983, 2 tapes (Box 1)
  - Richard Crawford, November 1, 1983, 2 tapes (Box 1)
  - Hazen Schumacher, September 20, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Hazen Schumacher, October 4, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Morris Lawrence Jr., September 27, 1983, 3 tapes (Box 1)
  - Richard Watson, October 25, 1983, 2 tapes (Box 2)
  - Theodore Grenier, October 18, 1983, 2 tapes (Box 2)
  - Louis Smith, January 31, 1984 (Box 2)
  - Ed Nelson, January 24, 1984 (Box 2)
  - J.C. Heard, November 22, 1983 (Box 2)
  - Kim Heron, February 7, 1984 (Box 2)
- Other materials
  - Grant applications (Box 2)
  - Grant file (NEA) (Box 2)
  - Art Fair (Box 2)
  - Correspondence (Box 2)
  - Term paper and clipping re: Eclipse Jazz (Box 2)
  - Newsletters (Box 2)
  - Programs (Box 2)
  - Posters and flyer notices for concerts (Box 3)